<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prose: on Magazine</title>
    <link>http://magzine.uk/tags/prose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prose: on Magazine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 20:50:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://magzine.uk/tags/prose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Washed Out</title>
      <link>http://magzine.uk/posts/washed-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 20:50:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://magzine.uk/posts/washed-out/</guid>
      <description>Rain. The heavy pitter-patter outside. On the roof. In the garden. On the terrace. Filling what it can and running down, over, around what it can&amp;rsquo;t.&#xA;And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter now. From the flat roof, yesterday I could see far across and I saw a light wink out in the dusk. Too bad, too good, too gone.&#xA;Around here the heat hung above the sky with the haze that turned all the sunsets orange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Aberration In Thought</title>
      <link>http://magzine.uk/posts/an-aberration-in-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 18:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://magzine.uk/posts/an-aberration-in-thought/</guid>
      <description>I get so emotional sometimes&amp;hellip;&#xA;I had arrived at the hospital to visit a friend. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen her for 14 years before the previous time which was some months ago. And now I wanted to visit - as at our age you never know.&#xA;There were freshly planted trees dotted across the plaza. They were mere saplings - young upstarts - and the delicate pale leaves fluttered slightly in a breeze that wasn&amp;rsquo;t there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Break</title>
      <link>http://magzine.uk/posts/the-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 23:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://magzine.uk/posts/the-break/</guid>
      <description>All I can hear as I lie here is the sound of my breathing. Far off below, lies the city, but no sound makes it up the hill through my thick curtains.&#xA;The large low room is dark, daylight held at bay. Life, oh life. I&amp;rsquo;m alive and last I night thought I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be. It was her, she led me there, but then she was one who many would follow.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
